webnetclick.com 2013-05-31

# Privacy Policy

| 

##  WebNetClick.com Privacy Policy

Our privacy policies exceed industry standards. Webnetclick Directory demands we restrict our use of information to only what is required to give you the best possible service,nothing more, nothing less. We want you our valued clients to read our Privacy Statement and to make up your own mind. If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, please contact our support staff by sending an email us from support@webnetclick.com marked Private. Please note that as a web and business directory this site contains links to other sites. Webnetclick Web Directory is not in any way responsible for the privacy practices, privacy statements, or content of these other sites.

###  Information Collection

We never intentionally collect personally identifying information from users of our site unless the user explicitly and intentionally enters it, or attempts to violate our security systems. Webnetclick Web Directory is the only owner of the information collected on the web sites listed. We offer users the ability to enter personally identifying information at several different points on our web site.

###  Registration (Sign-Up)

In order to use our web directory for editing, you may contact us from support@webnetclick.com. During this process describe the changes you wish us to make regarding your existing description our Added URL. In this case we use this information to verify the ownership, users must provide a valid email address. In addition to personally identifying and company information, a user must provide payment information for some listings.. This information is used for editing purposes according to requested services and terms of service agreement, and to fulfill customer's needs. If we have trouble processing an order, personal and company information is used to contact the user.

###  Delivery of Services

We collect information about servers connected to the IPs or URLs given by the users during the listing process. IP's and URL's are checked to verify users authority to do invasive port scanning, and/or vulnerability and penetration testing. No invasive data is collected until the user requests it and is verified as having proper authority to request the data to be collected. We only collect information that can be accessed from the internet about users computer(s) we do not install software on the users computers. We store information that we collect through your online listing/s which creates a profile for our users. A listing is then stored as information that we keep on individual users that details their viewing and services preferences. Consequently, collected information is tied to the user's personally identifiable information to provide other interested parties relevant information about the users listed site. This profile is used to tailor a user's visit to our Web site, and to direct pertinent marketing promotions for our listed clients.

###  Cookies

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. We use only session cookies and do not use persistent cookies. A session cookie simply terminates once users close the browser. Third Party Advertising We do not allow any third parties, including partners or advertisers, to collect information about users that can be linked to their company or personally identifying information.

###  Customer Service Communications

We communicate with users on a regular basis to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their account we reply via email. Legal Disclaimer Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information if and when required by law enforcement authorities and that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Company. This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement is solely intended for Webnetclick Web Directory. In order for this us to accurately provide for our users it is necessary for us to supplement the information we receive from third party sources.

###  Correcting/Updating/Deleting/Deactivating Personal Information

If a user's personally identifiable information or listing circumstances changes (such as website details, email etc), or if a user no longer desires our service, we provide a way to correct, update or delete/deactivate users. personally identifiable information. This can usually be done at the Registered User account or by emailing our Customer Support at support@webnetclick.com

###  Contact Information

If users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy statement including privacy, information use, collection, or security, please contact us at: Email: support at webnetclick dot com. Thank you for submitting your sites with Webnetclick.com Web Directory webnetclick Team

|
